[
  { 
    "question": "Tell us something about your __________ in the engineering industry?", 
    "answers": ["foreground", "background", "knowledge", "history"], 
    "correctAnswer": "background"
  },
  {
    "question": "I see from your __________ form that you have had three different jobs in the last 5 years.",
    "answers": ["apply", "applying", "applied", "application"],
    "correctAnswer": "application"
  },
  {
    "question": "What sort of __________ of time would you stay with us if we offered you the job?", 
    "answers": ["span", "duration", "period", "long"], 
    "correctAnswer": "period" 
  },
  {
    "question": "Describe how you would describe __________ in five years' time.", 
    "answers": ["you", "your", "yours", "yourself"], 
    "correctAnswer": "yourself" 
  },
  {
    "question": "Give us some idea of what you believe are your __________ and weaknesses.", 
    "answers": ["strength", "strengths", "force", "forces"], 
    "correctAnswer": "strengths" 
  },
  {
    "question": "As this is a managerial post, we must ask you how you deal with bad __________ keeping or unpunctuality in an employee.", 
    "answers": ["house", "space", "time", "record"], 
    "correctAnswer": "time" 
  },
  {
    "question": "Imagine one of your staff loses her temper and shouts at you in front of others, how would you __________ with this? ", 
    "answers": ["take", "do", "handle", "deal"], 
    "correctAnswer": "deal" 
  },
  {
    "question": "What would you say to a member of your staff who always __________ his work in late?", 
    "answers": ["delivered", "handed", "produced", "completed"], 
    "correctAnswer": "handed" 
  },
  {
    "question": "I should explain that we would naturally __________ any previous holiday arrangements you have made.", 
    "answers": ["believe", "show", "decide", "honour"], 
    "correctAnswer": "honour" 
  },
  {
    "question": "Finally now that we've asked you several questions, do you want to __________ any to us? ", 
    "answers": ["place", "put", "offer", "consider"], 
    "correctAnswer": "put" 
  }
]